THE TRUNK
SORRY, I'M GOING TO BE LATE
I'LL BE THERE SOON
Hurry up before some other guy
finds me in this dress.
Love you, babe!
31,306 VIEWS
PLEASE HELP MY DAUGHTER
WHO'S FALLEN FOR A MARRIAGE SCAM
SB ELECTRONICS SEO'S SEX TAPE
ONE DAY, MY DAUGHTER BROUGHT HOME
A MAN SHE WANTED TO MARRY…
…I FOUND OUT THAT HE'S A BISEXUAL
WHO'S USING MY DAUGHTER
5 YEARS AGO, 10 DAYS BEFORE THE WEDDING
I see you canceled
three days before the ceremony.
There's a 70% cancellation fee
if it's three to five days
before the ceremony.
You'll get a 30% refund.
It takes two weeks
for the transaction to go through.
We just need your signature here.
Excuse me. Sorry.
But did you lose this, by any chance?
So it is yours. I thought so.
I just found it in the bathroom.
You must've left it there.
I was throwing it away.
Take it if you want.
I don't care anyway.
Wait, but it's a wedding ring.
So why'd you get divorced?
Or, um, how'd you fall for someone
who swings both ways, huh, Ms. Noh?
Lee Seon. Hello.
Corporate operations management.
I'm also the CEO of NM.
LEE SEON, CEO
First, I'm supposed to pay
some sort of cancellation fee.
Now you wanna analyze what kind of woman
would cancel her own wedding
three days before.
You gonna give me a survey, or…
I have a proposal as the CEO.
I need someone suited for…
temporary marriages.
This employee would have
a different assignment every year.
It would be a C-suite level salary,
not to mention bonuses and full benefits.
Sound good?
A temp… what now?
What's so great about marriage anyway,
ya know?
Maybe it's your fault
for wanting an extravagant ceremony.
Wanting to show off.
You might've avoided all this, hmm,
if both of you had just gone off together.
Was it the attention? The recognition?
Did it matter that much to you?
Is that it, Ms. Noh?
Please. You obviously don't know shit.
It could become a career.
Think of marriage as a profession.
It might solve a lot of issues.
You could think of it as revenge,
if you will.
THE TRUNK
I'm heading straight
to the ER, okay?
We'll be there in ten. No, five.
Okay?
I'm gonna give you a shot.
You'll feel a slight prick.
Han Jeong-won?
What are you doing here?
Visiting your father?
Actually, no.
You might as well since you're here.
This hospital has around-the-clock care
and top-notch medical staff.
He doesn't need me right now.
But still, don't you think you…
Just call me when he passes.
I'll stop by then to grieve.
Ingrate.
NEW NOTIFICATION FROM NM
REQUEST KEEPER DISPATCH?
NO
I'll make sure
it doesn't leave a scar. Don't worry.
A little more to the side
and it would have dropped on your head.
You got really lucky.
It was almost a lot worse.
And listen, some people aren't worth
the pain and suffering.
You barely know me.
Wait, is that part of
the company handbook?
Well, usually,
letting your husband get impaled
doesn't look great
on a performance review.
You think we could pick up some burgers
since I saved your life? I'm super hungry.
Two cheeseburger combos,
and one with no tomatoes, please.
All right. We'll have that ready soon.
Two cheeseburger combos.
Thank you. Enjoy.
Thank you.
Something wrong?
Yeah, I'm a vegetarian, actually.
Should've told them no tomatoes,
that's all.
That was pretty funny.
No tomatoes, huh?
Do you like tomatoes?
No.
Let's vow that our salads
will never have tomatoes.
We better clean that. It'll get worse.
So can I ask you a question?
Sure. What?
- Which marriage are you on?
- This is number five.
Oh.
Does marriage…
help you live a better life?
Do you like it enough… to do it for work?
I think it's my turn.
You asked me, like, four things.
Why do you hate that light fixture, huh?
Who said there's something wrong with it?
It was pretty clear, honestly.
Come on. You wouldn't even look at it.
We should take off soon.
I asked Mr. Kim
to take care of it.
I still have help, even though
I don't like people coming in and out.
Let 'em know if you want anything.
Stop bitching!
Here, I got it.
I'm sorry. My hand slipped.
I don't usually eat breakfast,
so you're off the hook.
I do though.
Then just order something.
I don't wanna have to think about it.
All right, I should head out.
To do what?
Meetings. That's all.
You can come back for supper, right?
I'll wait for you.
Can I borrow your car?
Sure, whatever. Pick any of them.
So he's got meetings?
So who's this woman you're marrying?
Uh, you wouldn't know her, all right?
Sure. That's bullshit.
I know everyone.
So just tell me. Who is she?
Seo-yeon introduced us.
Lee Seo-yeon introduced you guys?
And so you just agreed?
She swore she'd take me back
if I do it for a year.
All right.
Two peas in a fucking pod, huh?
You guys are nuts.
I don't even wanna know
what the hell is going on in your heads.
Question is, what's our newlywed husband
doing here so early?
It's awkward.
What is?
Because of me, the lady, she…
she got hurt.
She probably doesn't want me
around right now.
You guys… moved in together? Already?
Everything's fine. I told you.
Well, it left
computerized medical records,
so the procedures here are
a little more complicated.
You get it, don't you?
Was there any violence or abuse?
Uh, no.
Were you vulnerable
to potential violence or abuse?
Again, no.
Do you anticipate
any future acts of violence or abuse?
Please reach out
if a code situation arises.
The keepers will remain on standby.
Oh, uh…
Yes?
Uh, nothing.
Hmm.
I don't like what I'm seeing here.
The inflammation doesn't look good.
I think we should take out your IUD.
Have you considered freezing your eggs?
Well, no. I don't plan
on getting pregnant.
Well, you might wanna
think about it for a bit--
Hey, I said no!
Let's switch out your IUD and take a beat.
That sound good to you?
Wait, you didn't hear?
I guess that woman protected Jeong-won
when that expensive chandelier thing
fell down and almost smashed his skull.
So is he… is he hurt?
Oh, I'm sure he's okay, but…
Well, apparently,
the woman's arm got a massive cut,
and she had to be rushed to the ER.
Is that true though?
Sounds exaggerated, for sure.
I know!
Still, it was heroic, don't you think?
I doubt I would've done that.
Not a chance.
For her to put her body on the line
in a situation like that…
Sounds like she loves him or something.
Oh, that's right.
The next Heritage Lounge meetup
is scheduled for the 15th.
Oh, we have a guest lecturer too.
So you're coming, right?
Uh,
yeah.
I still can't sleep.
She's getting on my nerves.
I need you.
That woman got hurt because of me.
It's bothering me.
She's getting on my nerves.
…with the free kick
in the center of the park,
trying to build up play from the back
as they're so used to doing.
Do you think, Alex,
they need a plan B at times like this?
They are the type of team…
So you just left it that way?
It's a scratch. Don't worry.
Let's just watch soccer, okay?
What's your phone number?
I never actually saved it,
so I couldn't reach you.
Well, if you had called,
would you have said you'd be late, then?
Yeah.
I would've told you not to cook for me.
Not that you'd listen.
Here you go.
NOH IN-JI
Why do you like this kind of marriage?
And just answer me straight.
Well, it was about revenge.
That was why I started anyway.
Now I'm starting to see
I actually have a gift for this.
Now you tell me something.
How about why
you can't stand those lights?
My dad attached…
cameras to that chandelier…
to spy on my mother.
My mother was skinny,
but she could take a few punches,
for sure.
After a while,
she went insane.
Our house was a hellhole.
And he wouldn't take her to the hospital,
so no one knew about it.
Then her sleepwalking got so bad that I…
I just followed her around every night.
I was afraid she'd kill herself.
That was before
my father started beating me.
I could have tried to stop him,
and I still don't know…
why I didn't.
Yeah.
That's why I can't stand those lights.
I don't know why you'd go into all that.
You said you weren't going to charm me.
You said I should just try
to be myself, right?
And I've thought about it.
It makes no difference.
It's like telling a secret
to someone who's not there.
And you have to keep my secrets.
It's mandatory, isn't it?
This should help you sleep.
It's jasmine tea.
It's really good.
Once I'm done writing my book,
we should go on a trip.
That might work.
Let's just do it.
I know I can make it work.
Let's just go.
Come on, huh?
Hang on a sec. Hang on.
Hey.
- Hey!
- Hey, give me an answer.
One second.
Yeah, hello?
Yes.
WIFE
Uh, hello?
So?
He's sleeping, but I shouldn't…
but I shouldn't wake him.
He hasn't slept in days.
I mean, is it urgent?
His dad's in the hospital.
He's been sick for a while.
He's doing better now though.
Give me a sec. He should hear this.
That's okay.
Even if he came right now,
it wouldn't matter.
Please tell him I called.
His father is going to be totally fine.
Okay.
Okay, I'll relay that.
Did Jeong-won
take a bunch of pills tonight?
I mean, you said he's out.
Uh, no.
He fell asleep on his own.
Really?
Ah.
Okay.
- Hey, stop it! It's mine!
- No, I already said it's mine!
Hwan, hey!
Hwan gets a turn now, all right?
- I said it's mine!
- Hey! Keep it down!
- Hwan! Come on. Take turns!
- Get off me!
As if I don't have enough
on my plate this morning. Jesus!
I really can't drive today.
Just cut me a little slack.
And if I take a taxi,
I'm gonna throw up mid-ride.
- Oh God.
- What the fuck?
That little shithead.
What the… What the…
- What the fuck? What the fuck?
- They can hear you.
Shit like that don't come to their senses
until somebody smashes into their ass.
Oh, come on, calm down.
You're giving me motion sickness.
Oh, give me a break. Who got drunk, huh?
Right.
This is all my fault.
We won't have enough money to remodel
even after a bank loan.
Maybe we only fix half.
I guess. Or you could ask Jeong-won
and borrow some money.
What is he, UNICEF?
Though, I mean,
he's got so much money,
he probably wouldn't notice it's gone.
All right, I'll… see if the bank
will extend our credit line.
I make just enough to get by running
a tiny, hole-in-the-wall record label,
you know?
Honestly, having Jeong-won as an employee
is so disorienting.
Like, am I rich too, or what?
Hey, honey, could we move away?
'Cause I don't think Jeong-won
is ever gonna quit. Ever.
- Stop it!
- Give it to me. I wanna see it!
Ow, ow! He's hurting me!
He's twisting my arm!
I told you to cut it out!
I want it! Get off!
Oh, I hate you!
You're awake.
Did I… fall asleep out here?
I mean, I couldn't move you
to your room on my own.
So the hospital is first on the agenda.
We're going for you. It is your father.
It's a shame.
He was doing so well up until now.
It's a good thing
your wife was here though.
So you were on Jeju Island?
Yes.
Why didn't you drop dead last night?
In your sleep.
NO RECENT MISSED CALLS
Did Jeong-won
take a bunch of pills tonight?
I mean, you said he's out.
Uh, no.
He fell asleep on his own.
What are you doing?
Helping you take care of it.
Even if spouses watch their partners
do wrong, they aren't liable legally.
Unfortunately,
you gotta have a good lawyer.
That being said, I know one.
It's him.
You want revenge?
Thanks so much.
So looks like we won.
He's alive
but doesn't get to eat amazing food.
You do this for all your clients?
Do what?
You left something on my pillow.
It's like a little voodoo doll.
You keep it, and you poke it with needles.
Baby powder that's inside.
I could always go to sleep if I had it,
even if I was scared of thunderstorms.
Thanks to you…
I slept well
for the first time in six months.
It's good to hear that it worked.
"Wife."
That's how she's saved on your phone.
Have you talked to her?
That's not your concern. Stay out of it.
I'll take care of it.
She asked me if you took pills last night.
I doubt you'd do anything
she didn't want you to.
Plus, she hasn't cut you off.
She's the one
who recommended the pills, huh?
Please make sure those vinyl covers
are fitting properly up there.
- Okay.
- I want precision cuts on all the pieces.
- Mr. uh… Mr. Oh, uh, um…
- Sh! Shut up, all right!
HAN JEONG-WON
You picked up.
I'm sorry they contacted you
about my dad yesterday.
It's fine.
He really wasn't the best father-in-law,
but I owed the guy.
- Let's get a tea.
- Next time.
I have to go now.
All right.
I'll bring the lights over
when they get there.
Make sure to run up the bill.
You look pretty good.
I fell asleep on the sofa.
Conked out. Without pills too.
That did happen now and then, didn't it?
Look, I better head out.
Right.
Ah Jesus.
Oh shit. I always forget this.
The passcode, what is it?
Oh great. Oh Christ.
Goddammit!
Sure, make yourself at home.
Yeah, you're one to talk, Ms. Do-dam.
That's my coffee machine, ya know.
Yeah, I know,
which is why I'm gonna get you one,
you bitchy tart.
Well, looks like I did you a favor, then.
You know how much cholesterol
is in three cups of this?
Oh, in that case,
feel free to pass on the coffee.
How can I resist
when it's just sitting there?
I get it.
Why are you here now?
Go to work, girl.
I warned you. You're destined
to bust your ass for table scraps.
Astrology doesn't lie.
Aw, cool it! You don't think
I have it hard enough as it is?
I mean, you know
I have problems to deal with, right?
What kind of problems, huh?
- Remember that Eom Tae-seong guy?
- Who?
It's that asshole who was stalking In-ji.
They released him
from the mental institution.
Who knows what that bastard
might try next. You see the issue?
Turn him in! That's what taxes are for!
We can't involve the police.
Why?
We can't. We just can't.
Just listen. They'll let anyone off
with a slap on the wrist,
even if it's something serious.
A suspended sentence? It's bullshit.
Why do you spend so much energy
looking out for In-ji?
You've got enough to deal with.
I really don't care if I die.
I gotta take care of her.
Oh, sure.
What are you, a goddamn saint?
What exactly
did this creepy asshole do anyway?
Eom Tae-seong single-handedly
ruined In-ji's entire life!
If you knew what that shitheel did to her…
This is serious stuff.
Oh crap. You're kidding.
That's it. I'm gonna get him.
I'm gonna murder this guy.
It's about Eom Tae-seong.
I guess he's back.
- Thanks, guy.
- Yep. Go ahead.
You know, I was just thinking…
This is the perfect day
to enjoy a few cups
of nice, freshly brewed tea.
You were destined to have some, Ms. Lee.
Yes.
How's Jeong-won? Is he all right?
He's great, as far as I know.
That's why you have
that look on your face.
Well, I was the one
who arranged the whole situation.
That sounds like… a test to me,
is that right?
You're doing this because you want him
all to yourself, but he's elusive.
You probably want to be
in control though, right?
I have to say,
I don't think I'm that twisted though.
No.
Absolutely not, dear.
Sorry. Uh, the man who'll be leading
our gathering is waiting.
He'd like to introduce himself.
Allez!
Allez! That's a hit.
Can I touch you?
Uh, no.
Then what are you doing here?
I came to see you.
I guess I shouldn't have.
Just go away. Get outta here, okay?
Come on. Time to go!
Get 'em out.
Sorry, folks.
I need everybody to clear out.
Please go home. Thank you.
Hey, they can't go this way!
That chest wound
must've been the lethal one.
I wonder how many there are.
What?
In the water.
There's gotta be lots of fish out there.
I dunno if it's 'cause I quit cigarettes.
This thing is making me hungry.
There's a loach soup place
down the road
and an entrail soup place
right next to it.
Hey, wrong direction. It's the other way.
I fell asleep on the sofa.
Conked out. Without pills too.
Uh, no. He fell asleep on his own.
Hi, Mr. Kim. I wanna head over there.
Will you let them know?
I'm Lee Seo-yeon. Uh, Jeong-won's ex-wife.
Hi.
Noh In-ji. Pleasure.
- Let's raise it two keys.
- All right, two keys up.
Yo, let's knock off early.
Go to a fancy restaurant.
Come on.
Sorry, dude. Don't think I can right now.
Why not?
Eating at home tonight.
Oh my God. I'm sorry.
My hands keep slipping.
It's all right.
I'll just use the bathroom.
Sure.
NOH IN-JI
DO YOU TRUST HER?
The number you have dialed
is no longer in service.
Please hang up and dial…
Do you trust that woman?
- Who?
- That woman.
The one Seo-yeon set you up with.
You think she's gonna be on your side?
Just keep your guard up
so she doesn't screw you over.
So you're saying
Ms. Noh In-Ji is the owner of that trunk?
Yes.
Whenever she got a new post,
she'd take it with her.
- "Post," you said?
- Yeah.
What does she do for work?
I don't know any specifics,
but she'd get sent all over the place.
You mean to tell me
you don't even know where she works?
You're best friends?
Are you familiar with that leaked video
from the Blooming Hotel?
The scandal
completely ruined her marriage.
We stopped talking after that.
Mm.
I understand.
When we first bought the house,
I decided to renovate the entire interior.
Well, except the chandelier, of course.
I assumed
it would be perfect for the space.
But now I feel bad for keeping it,
given what happened.
It's not a problem, Seo-yeon.
Things always get broken.
Well, I ordered some new lights
from France.
Jeong-won asked me to, actually.
Right.
That's enough small talk for now.
You know who I am.
Don't you have a question?
You know who I am, right?
Yeah, I do.
You are the architect, Lee Seo-yeon.